winning at all costs means putting
yourself at risk and putting others at
risk
when at all costs means doing whatever
you can to win
even if it's not always the right thing
that goes back to your coaching staff of
course like here at the academy they
never do that
but in some places their coaches will
tell you to do that
to do whatever it takes when it all
crosses when you
cheat or you take back roads that will
help you
get to where you need to be and it's
usually not an honest way
to win like waiting even if you have to
cheat and anything like that you just
want to win really bad
i feel like it can kind of be a dirty
like when it all costs can be like
you do whatever you can to win but
sometimes it cannot like it won't be a
good thing
because like you can do like doping like
for an example which isn't good
but it could also be like give it all
you thought
i think it depends on the situation it
can be a good thing if
you're not like sacrificing something
that would hurt someone else or hurt you
in a way
but if it's with good intentions like if
you're trying to win at all costs with
integrity i think that's good
[Music]
you